

CONTACT

Q Pa

Panipat, Haryana



+91-8954021471



yuktakakkar.yk@gmail.com



https://github.com/yuktakakkaryk



linkedin.com/in/yukta-kakkar-129380a9/

https://yuktakakkaryk.github.io/Portfolio

July 2019 - Present

Yukta Kakkar

A Computer Science and Engineering graduate, working with Capgemini as a Software Developer. With over 3 years of experience as a developer and a UI designer, my knowledge and skills can help to create an effective solution. Confident communicator, strategic thinker and an innovative creator to develop the product to meet an organization needs.

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- JQuery
- ReactJS
- Pentaho
- MongoDB
- MySQL

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe XD
- Adobe Illustrator
- Figma
- CorelDraw
- Wireframing
- Storyboarding

Work Experience

Associate Consultant

Capgemini Technology Services, Bangalore, India

Web Developer

 Developed the UI design for a shipment service company using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and Javascript.

• Report Designer

- Designed and developed static and interactive reports using Pentaho as a tool for a shipment service company.
- Used Pentaho Report Designer and Pentaho Data Integration to create the static reports and used CDE Dashboard to create the interactive reports.
- Used MySQL and JQuery to search and filter the data.
- Used MongoDB to store the collection.

UI Designer

- Created wireframe for the Interview Scheduling Application.
- Designed templates for powerpoint presentation for the organization.
- Designed CV templates for the organization.
- o Used Adobe XD, Figma, Photoshop and Illustrator as the

Extra-Curricular

December 2020 – February 2021

Scheduler

Capgemini Technology Services, Bangalore, India

- Assisted HR Department with the interview process.
- Worked as a scheduler to schedule the interviews between the interviewer and the interviewee.

June 2018 - August 2018

Content Writer

GadgetsDesk, Dehradun, India

- Contributed and completed an internship at GadgetsDesk as a content writer for three months.
- Wrote around 7-8 articles for the digital paper regarding the emerging new technologies. <u>Certificate Link</u>

Education

July 2015 - May 2019

2014 - 2015

2012 - 2013

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science

Graphic Era University, Dehradun

CGPA: 8.20

Class XII (CBSE)

Bal Vikas Progressive School, Panipat

Class X (CBSE)

Bal Vikas Progressive School, Panipat

Projects

Portfolio

Created a portfolio using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JQuery where I have showcased all about myself and my work.

Portfolio Link

Click here to view the source code

CV Generator

Created a CV Generator using HTML, CSS and Javascript using which you can create and manage several different resumes in an organised way automatically.

Click here to view the source code

• Expense Tracker

Created an Expense Tracker using HTML, CSS, Javascript and ReactJS where you can keep an accurate record of your money inflow and outflow.

Click here to view the source code

• Stone, Paper, Scissors

Created a simple game – Stone, Paper, Scissors using HTML, CSS and Javascript which can be played with the computer as the second player.

Click here to view the source code

Word Counter

Created a word counter application using HTML, CSS and Javascript which helps the user to count the number of words and characters in a document or passage of text.

Click here to view the source code

ToDo List

Created a todo list using HTML, CSS and Javascript which helps the user list all the tasks to be done and delete and edit a particular task as well.

Click here to view the source code

A Simple Calculator

Created a simple calculator using HTML, CSS and Javascript which helps user to perform basic mathematical functions.

Click here to view the source code

Watch Movies

Search a variety of movies of your choice and watch them on IMDB.

Click here to view the source code